janjuaplayer.com 2018-11-29

# Privacy policy - JanJua.tv

Privacy policy:

**General**

janjua is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the janjua website. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information janjua collects about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom janjua discloses it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. Please read carefully. 

**Collection of Information**

janjua may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of the website. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of the website's user base, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by janjua and other third-party advertising providers during your use of the janjua website and in serving advertisements to the janjua website.

janjua may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on the janjua website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the janjua website places onto the user's computer hard drive. Cookies identify the user's computer hard drive so that the janjua website can recognize you the next time you visit.

Third party advertisements displayed on or in connection with the janjua website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. janjua does not control these cookies and users of the janjua website should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether and how it uses cookies. 

**Use of Information**

If you submit personally identifiable information to janjua through the janjua website, then janjua may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.

janjua does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. 

**Disclosure of Information**

janjua will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties for their commercial or marketing use.

janjua may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

janjua also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that, in good faith, if appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the janjua website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of janjua, our users or others. 

**Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**

This privacy notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review it periodically to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the janjua website constitutes your agreement to this privacy notice and any future revisions.
